{
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "Javascript is an _______ language?",
      "options": [
        "Object-Oriented",
        "Object-Based",
        "Procedural",
        "None of the above"
      ],
      "answer": "Object-Oriented"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following methods is used to access HTML elements using Javascript?",
      "options": [
        "getElementById()",
        "getElementByClassName()",
        "Both",
        "None of the above "
      ],
      "answer": "Both"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following methods can be used to display data in some form using Javascript?",
      "options": [
        "document.write()",
        "window.alert()",
        "console.log()",
        "All of the above"
      ],
      "answer": "All of the above"
    },
    {
      "question": "When the switch statement matches the expression with the given labels, how is the comparison done?",
      "options": [
        "Both the datatype and the result of the expression are compared.",
        "Only the datatype of the expression is compared.",
        "Only the value of the expression is compared.",
        "None of the above  "
      ],
      "answer": "Both the datatype and the result of the expression are compared."
    },
    {
      "question": "What keyword is used to check whether a given property is valid or not?",
      "options": [
        "in",
        "contain",
        "exists",
        "lies"
      ],
      "answer": "in"
    },
    {
      "question": "When an operator’s value is NULL, the typeof returned by the unary operator is:",
      "options": [
        "Boolean",
        "Undefined",
        "Object",
        "Integer"
      ],
      "answer": "Object"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does the Javascript “debugger” statement do?",
      "options": [
        "It will debug all the errors in the program at runtime.",
        "It acts as a breakpoint in a program.",
        "It will debug error in the current statement if any.",
        "All of the above   "
      ],
      "answer": "It acts as a breakpoint in a program."
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the output of the code snippet - print(NaN === NaN); ?",
      "options": [
        "true",
        "false",
        "undefined",
        "error"
      ],
      "answer": "false"
    },
    {
      "question": "What will be the output of the following code snippet - print(typeof(NaN)); ?",
      "options": [
        "Object ",
        "Number ",
        "String ",
        "None of the above    "
      ],
      "answer": "Number "
    },
    {
      "question": "What does the “toLocateString()“ method do in JS?",
      "options": [
        "Returns a localised object representation.",
        "Returns a parsed string.",
        "Returns a localized string representation of an object.",
        "None of the above.     "
      ],
      "answer": "Returns a localized string representation of an object."
    }
  ]
}
